This area here, between the eyebrows, indicates when someone is truly in pain,
or experiencing suffering,
whether it's physical, emotional, or otherwise. You'll see it here, and in the eyes as well, you see the eye almost twitching, like that.
There is a geometry in the iris that can manifest this way, that...
It's also a point of initiation that is related to
the...
The shape of the brain, at first, it is flat.
And through the process of telencephalization, it does this.
This is where you establish the crystallization.
It’s a point of concentration.
We call it the eye of clairvoyance.
You have clairvoyance.
Here, we use the emotion of the other.
I will play with your astral plane.
And then, you have clairvoyance.
That is, you start seeing the world clearly.
of the other. It means you see how they function. That's already a form of clairvoyance.
That happens here. And then, there is the third and unique clairvoyance, which is polyvoyance.
You start to see God or divinity in everything. You have
an electromagnetic spectrum.
This is what we see. You see, if I have grown, actually, that's already significant. It’s our rainbow
of light.
But look at what it represents as a reality, you see, around us.
Everything that exists, all these frequencies, the more you enhance your abilities,
sometimes you can see things a bit outside.
The eye will receive luminous information, so it will receive a photon.
The very first layer to be crossed will be the conjunctiva.
The second layer to be crossed will be the cornea.
The cornea, which is the front part...
of the sclera in front that is transparent.
Then, you will have the passage through the pupil.
So, the first chamber in front is the anterior chamber
which contains aqueous humor.
Anterior chamber, the iris with the pupil here that
passes.
And there, you have a so-called posterior chamber
that contains the same fluid.
But you have in front here what we call the ciliary processes
that will also produce
fluid and a bit further back here from what we call the limbus, you will have
the canal
of Schlemm or sclera which comes to reabsorb so that
there is continuously a fluid that
circulates here, which lives, which nourishes, and then it will cross and meet what
we
call the crystalline accommodation, and at the level of the crystalline, the vitreous humor
that crosses to
arrive at my
retina, which is made of different layers. So not only do I take just a small
light spectrum, but I am still capable of perceiving the smallest amount
of light possible, which is called a photon. Additionally, I have a narrowed field.
I have a
possible vision that is a centered vision, and I also have a very interesting vision,
which is peripheral vision. I must learn to use these two visions. So a frequency,
a wave.
and a spectrum that, at maximum, varies in tetrade of
5 degrees,
actually even compared to 23 degrees, but I will explain that a bit later.
It’s a 23 degrees like the orientation of your heart,
like the orientation of the Earth, like the orientation of your inner ears.
There are specific angles in the body.
It will go to the retina, causing what we call the transduction phenomenon,
this level of photons into electricity.
into a nerve impulse that will be transmitted to
the left and right,
for each eye every time, at the level of what we call the LGN,
so the lateral geniculate nucleus,
which will give an interpretation, how it will integrate this information,
parvocellular, magnocellular, and koniocellular,
which will contain specific information.
Then it will come later, once it is...
It will take what we call the optical radiations to go toward the
visual cortex, above and below the calcarine fissure.
Very interesting, very important to know how to localize.
This famous journey, the eye, all the interpretation we see here,
and these radiations towards these cortical areas and towards the different
levels of interpretation.
that we will look at a little bit in detail now.